# Joann Pilika

DESIGNER

jp4926.myportfolio.com joann.pilika@nyu.edu /in/joannpilika/

#### **SKILLS**

Design Skills

UX design

Logo design

Computer Skills

Microsoft Office

MacOS + iOS

Design tools

Adobe Animate

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe InDesign

Adobe After Effects

Adobe Premiere Pro

Adobe XD

Final Cut Pro X

**Programming Skills** 

Python

Javascript

HTML5 & CSS

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

# Tandon Scholarship Recipient

Fall 2017

Academic and merit-based scholarship

# **Oustanding General Engineering Design**

Spring 2018

Nominee for Nick Russo

Award

# Geometry/Trigonometry Award

Spring 2017

Newman School of Boston annual academic awards

## PERSONAL STATEMENT

Joann Pilika is a 19 year old student at the Tandon School of Engineering, New York University. She studies Integrated Digital Media, concentrating on media studies, design, and computer science. She is interested in working in website development and user experience design with a focus on graphic design.

Experienced in social media and managing accounts, with extensive knowledgeable in brand social media, she has run social media for two small businesses. She has interned with Living Proof as a Graphic Designer in which she learned the ins and outs of an in-house Creative team and worked closely with the Marketing team.

#### **EDUCATION**

New York University Sep 2017 - Present BS in Integrated Digital Media Tandon School of Engineering

Newman School Sep 2013 -

May 2017

Internationale Baccalaureate Diploma Program

Head prefect of student body; Captain of women's basketball & lacrosse teams.

### **EXPERIENCE**

 Tandon Online New York, NY Feb 2019 - Present Studio & Video Production Assistant

Assist in creating graphics for online courses offered at NYU's graduate, engineering school. Implemented motion graphics in lecture videos and collaborated with team on deciding course themes.

NYU Tandon New York, NY Jun 2018 - Present **Teaching Assistant** 

Teach workshop classes to class of first-year students on invention, innovation, and engineering. Foster an innovative atmosphere in class and guide students with their semesterlong start-up projects.

Living Proof Boston, MA

Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

Graphic Design Intern

Designed product guides and PowerPoint templates for brand. Assisted creative and marketing teams in organizing assets in cloud system. Resized images and graphics as requested by vendors.

Abercrombie & Fitch Jul 2018 - Feb 2019 **Brand Agent** 

Organized on-campus events for Abercrombie & Fitch to promote brand awareness. Posted on personal social media as an ambassador and reported engagement analytics weekly. Represented Abercrombie & Fitch at NYU and in New York City.